[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Colorado River, the major river of the American southwest, flows through which national landmark?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The Hoover Dam", "The Grand Canyon", "Arches National Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character is the adoptive father of Princess Leia?", "correct_answer": "Bail Organa", "incorrect_answers": ["Obi Wan Kenobi", "Shmei Skywalker", "Yoda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are  the odds that you will be killed by lightning in the USA?", "correct_answer": "2,320,000 to 1", "incorrect_answers": ["360,200,000 to1", "23,200,000 to 1", "506,000 to 1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leg extensions are safer for your knees than squats.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the greatest common factor (GCF) of 24 and 36?", "correct_answer": "12", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "6", "14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Hammerfest, which is often referred to as the northernmost town in Europe, is located in this Scandinavian country.", "correct_answer": "Norway", "incorrect_answers": ["Finland", "Switzerland", "Sweden"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which famous brothers directed the 1996 movie Kingpin?", "correct_answer": "Bobby and Peter Farrelly", "incorrect_answers": ["Joel and Ethan Cohen", "Tony and Ridley Scott", "Andy and Larry Wachowski"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Also the name of a famous vodka, Finlandia was a symphonic poem first written in 1899 by what Finnish composer?", "correct_answer": "Jean Sibelius", "incorrect_answers": ["Frederic Chopin", "Edvard Grieg", "Magnus Lindberg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The carrot was outlawed in Holland in the 16th century.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ophiuchus is on the ecliptic.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie by the same name, what part of the African Queen gets severely damaged in the trip down the rapids?", "correct_answer": "The propeller and shaft", "incorrect_answers": ["The steam rotor", "The tiller rod", "The boiler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first physician to demonstrate that arteries carry blood throughout the body?", "correct_answer": "Galen", "incorrect_answers": ["Valen", "Valecious", "Herodotus"]}]